{
    "id": "21c1d5bb559d4996b21c28e9f29c252b",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She grew up ……………. Mexico.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He gets to the market ……………….. bike.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "in",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you looking ……………… me like that?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked ……………….. the children to have extra milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Sorry, I couldn’t phone yesterday – I was ………………… the theater.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is very hot ……………… the center of the earth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "That picture would look better ………………. the other wall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s go for a walk ………………… the woods.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It took five days to cross the Atlantic ……………… the Queen Elizabeth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The manager is not ……………… his cabin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}